Hi everyone, I'm jin jiewan.
I will demonstrate how to interact with my movie recommendation system and the 4 options that can be chosen from.
As you can see the movie first, welcome us and it will ask us some questions that it will according to the questions to recommend movies from the top 250 movies.
And firstly, let's answer the questions on the screen.
Let's say we want a new movie, not an old one.
So we answer questions.
Just one, but one.
And now the system has a series of recommendation movies and will choose from the 2 options to have check to choose which mode we will.
Like to check the movies.
Let's say we just want the simple mode, so it just shows us the titles of the movies that is recommended, which are 2 movies.
Let's say we want to check the plot of the movies from the next 2 options, so we enter one.
And we will check the first movie, the movie one which is up.
So we still enter one and it shows that the plot of the movie up.
That is a 78 years old Carl, blah, blah, blah.
And then if we want to check the link of the movies, we will enter 2.
And we enter one to check the link of the movie up.
So it direct us to the website of the movie from the IMDB website.
And we can see more details on the website.
And then we return to our program.
Let's say we don't want more information, so we.
And exit.
And we.
I will play it again to review the process.
And then I will answer questions very quick.
And this time I will check the first option.
That is the detailed mood.
So it gives us many details about the movies, such as ranking the genres, year it release, the director and the run time.
I will see the link of the movies, so I enter to.
And I will check the link of the godfather part 2.
So I enter 2 for the second movie.
So we can see the link website of the movie as expected and an exit system.
So that's my demonstration of my program.
Hope you will like it and hope you will have a great winter break.
Bye.